

JENNY BORGLIN

**FORMER DIGITAL MARKETING COORDINATOR

PORTFOLIO

https://jennymalmoe.github.io/Portfolio/

GITHUB

https://github.com/jennymalmoe

LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/jenny-borglin-malmo/

PERSONAL PROFILE

Full Stack Development graduate at Code Institute, Ireland (University Credit-Rated Bootcamp) with 15 years of marketing, copy, communication, UX/UI and traffic experience.

I'm passionated about front end development and UX/UI. Seeking to further improve my back end skills.

I'm a quick learner and eager to learn new skills!

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, UX/UI, Wireframing, Python, Django, Flask, Jinja, SQL, AWS, Stripe Payment API, Bootstrap, Materialize, Responsive Design, Heroku, Testing and Debugging, Git Version Control.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Software Developer

CODE INSTITUTE, DUBLIN, IRELAND FEB 2021-DEC2021

- Coding Fundamentals (HTML, CSS)
- User-Centric Frontend Development (User Experience Design, Bootstrap etc.)
- Interactive Frontend Development (JavaScript, APIs, jQuery etc.)
- Data-Centric Development (Python, Flask, MySQL, Mongo etc.)
- Full-Stack Frameworks (Django, payment solutions)

Service Manager for future tourism, Field of specialization: Marketing

YRKESHÖGSKOLAN, MALMÖ

Leadership and Organization, Project development and Project management, Service management, Marketing, Business administration, Concept development, 12 weeks of internship etc.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Advertising Traffic Coordinator

ADONNEWS 2012 TILL 2021

Leading and co-ordinating campaigns from initial stages through to delivery. Copy, graphic design, communication with the advertiser, analyzing campaigns (visitor data and user experience), inputting ideas on how to improve current practices where required. Identifying and developing a strong understanding of client's core objectives and challenges.

Head of Google Ads Team

SCANDIADS 2010 TILL 2012

In charge of Google Ads sales team and result-oriented advertising and marketing campaigns designed to meet customer needs. Including budget management and copy.

Copywriter

3C-ADS A/S, COPENHAGEN 2006 TILL 2010

Ad copy Google Ads. Writing unique selling points, writing high-converting CTA ads etc.

CONTACT

Email: jenny.c.borglin@gmail.com

Phone: +46 70 553 40 14

Address: Flaggskeppsgatan 2, 211 14 Malmö